http://www.goincase.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Collection and Use of Personal Information
Personal information means any information that is related to an identified person, or that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to: first and last name; email address; a home, postal or other physical address or other contact information; title, gender, occupation, industry, or personal interests; and other personal information necessary or useful to provide a product or service that you have requested. The types of personal information we collect and what we do with that information are listed below.
Domain Name and IP Address
We collect the domain names and IP addresses of our visitors for statistical purposes, in order to measure use, to improve the content or responsiveness of our site or to customize the content or layout of the site for the individual visitor. We do not disclose this information to third parties. We may also aggregate information relating to our visitors' traffic patterns from the data that we collect and retain concerning the IP addresses and domain names of our visitors, and we may divulge such aggregate information about our users with third parties such as our business partners, distributors, and service and support providers.
You may visit our website anonymously if you wish, by using appropriate software or webservices available from or through third parties.
Log Files
We maintain a log file of all actions that are initiated or facilitated using our website in order to capture, record and store data concerning the transaction. Access to this data is restricted to internal usage by authorized Incase employees who administer our network and website.
E-Mail Address
You should know that e-mail is not necessarily secure against all forms of interception. If your communication includes sensitive information about you and you would prefer not to transmit this information in this fashion, please contact us by mail or telephone rather than e-mail. See "Oversight And Questions" section below for this contact information.
We collect e-mail addresses that are volunteered by the visitor, from e-mail messages addressed to our company or its employees, through visitor participation in surveys, contests and site registrations or provided by the visitor when placing an order on the site.
We use the e-mail addresses for marketing purposes and to inform those interested in our products about events, products, services or other items of interest. Additionally, we use the e-mail addresses to notify visitors about recent updates to our website, to provide product or service news notifications or to send newsletters and promotions. We also use the e-mail addresses to process orders for products, services, brochures and other written materials, to respond to customer questions, to provide customer service and to inquire as to customer satisfaction and feedback.
You may opt-out of receiving the promotional or marketing e-mails at any time by (1) specifying your preference at the time of creating your profile; (2) changing your e-mail preferences in any user profile that you may have created. If you choose to opt-out of receiving e-mails via any of the above listed methods, Incase's records will be updated within ten days of receipt of your request. These opt-out procedures will not be available for e-mails that are necessary to provide confirmation of a completed transaction (such as a purchase or change in the visitor's user profile).
Tell-A-Friend or Email Your Wish List
If you choose to use our referral service or to email your wish list, we will ask you for your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Incase does not store this information and uses it for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.
Credit Card Information
We collect credit card and billing information from visitors who make purchases from our online store. We use this information to bill the customer for product purchases. Credit card data will not be saved.
Collection and processing of credit cards is performed by the third-party service provider NetSuite, www.netsuite.com. Order delivery is performed by UPS, ups.com. These third party providers are not authorized or permitted to use personal information for any other reason other than those pertaining to processing order transactions.
Other Personal Information
When you register with our site, you provide other personal information including your name, mailing address, billing address and phone number. This information is used mainly to process orders placed on our online store and to facilitate customer service and the delivery of products you have ordered. We may also use a mailing address that a visitor provides for a variety of Incase-related reasons. We may send periodic mailings to visitors to inform our visitors who have provided a mailing address of new products, services or promotions. Your mailing address and telephone number may also be used to contact you about orders placed on-line or to provide information that you have requested.
If you do not wish to receive such mailings, you may request to be removed from the contact list by changing your account preferences in your user profile or email us.
If you post reviews or comments on the incase.com site and blog, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in comments on our blog. Please note that all product reviews are screened prior to posting and Incase will not post reviews containing personally identifiable information or inappropriate language.
Personal Information Released to Outside Parties
Any information that you provide to us will be used for our purposes only. Except as specified in this Policy, your information will not be shared with individuals outside the employ of Incase or with other companies.
In some instances we may provide your name and delivery address to third parties that we use for delivering specific products to you (such as delivery companies and other affiliates). The process of fulfilling orders placed via the online store may also require Incase to share your information with other third parties such as automated data processors and credit card processors. In such cases, your information is not retained by these third parties or used by these companies for any secondary reasons. We may also share customer information with our trusted third party service providers who provide advertising services using information that our customers provide, such as name, street address, email address, and transaction history, as further described below. Our trusted third parties are contractually prohibited from using customer information for any purpose other than to provide services to Incase. If you prefer Incase not to share your information with our third party service providers, please e-mail us at support@goincase.com. These opt-out procedures will not be available if you choose to purchase products via our online store or via telephone as forwarding information is necessary in order to facilitate such a transaction.
As a good corporate citizen, Incase complies with applicable law and legal obligations to respond to governmental, law enforcement and court requests for personal information and other information and data about our visitors and their transactions. Incase's legal counsel may access and use your personal information and other information or data in the event of a dispute, in response to legal process or law enforcement inquiries, abuse of our website, or violation of our Terms of Service Policy
Cookies
A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. To use portions of Incase's website you must set your browser to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.
Incase uses session cookies. These cookies are used when you type your login information during your visit to our site and are used for a variety of reasons such as to keep track of items in your shopping cart, to keep track of your login name and passwords and to mark a session timeout. The cookies are not tied to a visitor's personal information. This information is encrypted and stored in a cookie during that session. The cookie is deleted from the visitor's computer when the visitor logs out or closes his or her browser. Some of our business partners (e.g., service providers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.incase.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertiser.
Editing Your Personal Profile
We provide a means to create a personal account or profile of personal information when you register on the retail section of our site. We realize that your personal information, including your name and e-mail address, is subject to change. To the extent that you provide us with personal information, we wish to maintain its accuracy. Our goal is to provide a variety of means for you to contact us should you need to update or correct your personal information. Personal information is collected and stored by a third-party service provider NetSuite, www.netsuite.com. This third party provider is not authorized or permitted to use personal information for any other reasons than those pertaining to order transactions. To change or delete the information in your personal account, by selecting "My Account" on the top menu bar of the Store section of our site and follow the prompts to edit your profile. Additionally, you may request changes in your personal account or profile by contacting Incase. Any submitted changes to your account will occur within seven business days.
Data Security
Your store account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. We safeguard the security of the data you send us with certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We have taken reasonable precautions to protect against misuse, theft, loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of your personal information. Additionally, we use industry-standard 128-Bit SSL Encryption to enhance the security of data transmissions.
While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. We suggest that you change your passwords often, that your passwords include a combination of letters and numbers, and that you make certain that you are using a secure browser. Products and services are available which can help give you privacy protection while navigating the Web. See an overview of many privacy-related tools.
Data Forwarding
We maintain your personal information on servers and computers located in the United States and operated under our direct supervision and control. We do not forward your personal information outside the United States.
Data Quality
We will take reasonable steps to insure that all data collected is accurate, complete and timely for the purposes for which they are to be used. We urge you to check your profile regularly to insure that such information is accurate, complete and timely.
Children's Privacy
We do not structure our website to attract children. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect information from anyone who is age 13 and under.
California Consumer Privacy Act
For additional information on the California Consumer Privacy Act please click on the following link: Incipio Group California Consumer Privacy Act
Third Party Sites
Incase's website contains links to other sites. When you click on one of these links you are being transferred to a website operated by someone other than Incase, and the operator of that website may have a different privacy policy. Incase does not share your personal information with these websites and is not responsible for their individual privacy practices. We encourage you to investigate the privacy policies of these operators.
Future Changes
By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this Privacy Policy and to our Terms of Service Policy. Incase may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page or by notice on our homepage, so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will post a notice on this page for thirty (30) calendar days prior to the implementation of any material changes to this Privacy Policy. Such notice will provide information as to how you may remove your information from our database should you so desire.
Oversight and Questions
We welcome comments and questions on this policy. As stated above, we are dedicated to protecting your privacy, and we will make every reasonable effort to keep your information secure. Questions regarding our policy should be directed via e-mail or by telephone: 888-283-8288. Additionally you may contact us by writing to Incase at Incase Designs Corp., 3347 Michelson Drive, Suite 100, Irvine, CA 92612.
Dimensions
Compatibility
Material
View All
NewClearance
